<content-feed>
  <source>arutz-sheva-news</source>
  <source-type>rss</source-type>
  <feed-url>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/Rss.aspx</feed-url>
  <generated>2026-02-28T01:46:02.957704</generated>
  <count>10</count>
  <item id="1" rank="140">
    <title>Trump on Iran strike: I don't want to, but sometimes you have to</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;President Trump says he has not yet decided on military action against Iran, expresses dissatisfaction with the country's negotiations, but indicates further talks will take place.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North American desk is ke...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677167</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:01:56 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="2" rank="135">
    <title>IAEA report highlights lack of access to Iran's nuclear sites after war</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;New IAEA report reveals Iran has denied access to nuclear sites bombed in June, leaving key details of its uranium stockpile unverified. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North American desk is keeping you updated until the start of Shabba...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677170</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:15:18 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="3" rank="130">
    <title>Countries warn citizens against travel to Israel and Iran amid rising tensions</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Several countries, including France, Britain, and Germany, advise citizens against traveling to Israel and Iran due to escalating tensions. Warnings include heightened security risks and possible border closures.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677169</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:32:12 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="4" rank="130">
    <title>IDF Spokesperson reassures Israelis amid rising tensions</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;IDF Spokesperson Effie Defrin reassures the public, saying the military is monitoring Iran closely and remains on high alert. This comes after the US Embassy in Israel announced staff evacuations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North Ame...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677168</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:43:25 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="5" rank="110">
    <title>'Peace is within reach': Omani FM optimistic after meeting US VP JD Vance</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Omani Foreign Minister Badr Albusaidi expresses hope for peace after meeting US VP JD Vance in Washington, discussing ongoing US-Iran talks. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North American desk is keeping you updated until the start of Sh...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677172</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:24:08 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="6" rank="105">
    <title>Trump: Iran is ‘not going far enough’ in nuclear negotiations</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;President Trump expresses frustration with Iran's refusal to make a more substantial deal on nuclear issues, emphasizing their lack of commitment to forgoing nuclear weapons. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North American desk is keeping...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677174</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:39:19 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="7" rank="105">
    <title>Rubio to visit Israel amid growing tensions with Iran</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US Secretary of State Marco Rubio will visit Israel from March 2-3 to discuss regional issues, including Iran, Lebanon, and Trump's 20-Point Peace Plan for Gaza.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel National News' North American desk is keeping you updated u...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677171</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:59:15 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="8" rank="90">
    <title>Rubio designates Iran a state sponsor of wrongful detention</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US Secretary of State Marco Rubio announced on Friday that he has designated Iran as a state sponsor of wrongful detention.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“The Iranian regime must stop taking hostages and release all Americans unjustly detained in Iran, steps that could end this d...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677173</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:31:25 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="9" rank="85">
    <title>'My seat was stolen': Cori Bush formally files bid to reclaim seat, blasts AIPAC</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Former Rep. Cori Bush files to reclaim her seat in Missouri, challenging incumbent Wesley Bell. She criticizes AIPAC's $8.6 million effort against her in 2024, and vows to fight for &amp;quot;Palestinian rights&amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Arutz Sheva-Israel Nationa...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/677175</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:57:30 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="10" rank="70">
    <title>Shabbat Shalom!</title>
    <summary>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Arutz Sheva-Israel National News&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; is stopping its round-the-clock news updates at this time in honor of the start of Shabbat in North America, where they are being written now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Updates will resume Saturday night from Israel, followi...</summary>
    <link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/flashes/629916</link>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0200</published>
    <original-source>arutz-sheva-news</original-source>
  </item>
</content-feed>