<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content-feed source="bbc-news" generated="2026-02-28T10:12:00.756308" count="38">
  <item>
    <title>Watch: Smoke rises in Tehran as explosions heard across country</title>
    <summary>The BBC's Jon Donnison in Jerusalem reports as Trump says "major combat operations" have begun.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:54:35 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mahmood to press on with immigration reforms despite by-election defeat</title>
    <summary>The home secretary is to double down on plans for Danish-style restrictions on asylum seekers.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:52:46 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Henry Zeffman: Green victory shows insurgent parties are here to stay</title>
    <summary>The party's historic win in Gorton and Denton by-election is clearest sign yet of changing political landscape.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:38:15 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Man charged after Churchill statue defaced, police say</title>
    <summary>Caspar San Giorgio, 38, of no fixed address was arrested on Friday, police say.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:44:50 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Boy assaulted by birth parents wins campaign for UK child cruelty register</title>
    <summary>Tony Hudgell, who lost both legs after his birth parents assaulted him, has fought to protect children.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:28:13 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The mystery man who links Andrew with Jeffrey Epstein</title>
    <summary>For nearly a decade, David Stern acted as a key conduit between Jeffrey Epstein and Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:00:27 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bill Clinton asked about hot tub photo and testifies he knew 'nothing' of Epstein crimes</title>
    <summary>The former president told the committee that he would never have flown on Epstein's plane if he "had any inkling of what he was doing".</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:43:56 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>At least 15 killed after military plane carrying banknotes crashes in Bolivia</title>
    <summary>Police fire tear gas to disperse crowds allegedly trying to take banknotes from the crash site.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:01:03 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Neil Sedaka, singer of Breaking Up Is Hard To Do, dies at 86</title>
    <summary>A skilled pianist nominated for five Grammy awards, Sedaka wrote hits through the 1950's and 60's.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:09:44 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rent tops £1,000 a month in more areas - find out where</title>
    <summary>The cost of renting privately has surged in the last five years, but tenants may now see a slowdown.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:14:04 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
</content-feed>
