<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content-feed source="bbc-news" generated="2026-02-28T12:10:57.877380" count="40">
  <item>
    <title>What we know about the joint US-Israel attack on Iran</title>
    <summary>Donald Trump has described "major combat operations", with explosions heard across Iran.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:06:22 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mahmood to press on with immigration reforms despite by-election defeat</title>
    <summary>The home secretary is to double down on plans for Danish-style restrictions on asylum seekers.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:06:30 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The mystery man who links Andrew with Jeffrey Epstein</title>
    <summary>For nearly a decade, David Stern acted as a key conduit between Jeffrey Epstein and Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:00:27 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bill Clinton asked about hot tub photo and testifies he knew 'nothing' of Epstein crimes</title>
    <summary>The former president told the committee that he would never have flown on Epstein's plane if he "had any inkling of what he was doing".</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:43:56 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Boy assaulted by birth parents wins campaign for UK child cruelty register</title>
    <summary>Tony Hudgell, who lost both legs after his birth parents assaulted him, has fought to protect children.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:28:13 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Henry Zeffman: Green victory shows insurgent parties are here to stay</title>
    <summary>The party's historic win in Gorton and Denton by-election is clearest sign yet of changing political landscape.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:38:15 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Neil Sedaka, singer of Breaking Up Is Hard To Do, dies at 86</title>
    <summary>A skilled pianist nominated for five Grammy awards, Sedaka wrote hits through the 1950's and 60's.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:09:44 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The strange British phenomenon of the snatched backseat picture</title>
    <summary>Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor is the latest in a long line of famous people photographed in the back of a car.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:00:55 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cruz Beckham launches music career, having fun amid family drama</title>
    <summary>Can David and Victoria's youngest son escape the "nepo baby" label and find success with his band?</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:14 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Six things to look out for in tonight's Brit Awards ceremony</title>
    <summary>Will there be a tribute to Ozzy Osbourne? And will Taylor Swift break her losing streak?</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:01:08 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
</content-feed>
