<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content-feed source="bbc-news" generated="2026-02-28T02:06:21.847866" count="41">
  <item>
    <title>Starmer vows to fight on after historic Green by-election win</title>
    <summary>The result - in a seat Labour has held for nearly 100 years - heaps further pressure on the PM's position.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 19:51:18 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Henry Zeffman: Green victory shows insurgent parties are here to stay</title>
    <summary>The party's historic win in Gorton and Denton by-election is clearest sign yet of changing political landscape.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:38:15 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Trump 'not thrilled' with Iran after latest talks on nuclear programme</title>
    <summary>President Trump said he was not happy with Iran's stance, but had not yet decided whether to attack.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:21:35 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Anxious days inside Iran as speculation grows of US strikes</title>
    <summary>To many, Iran now seems to be hovering in a tense limbo where everything could change suddenly.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:48:48 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'We were bullied for years before our son was killed'</title>
    <summary>The parents of 14-year-old Ibrahima Seck say they were being harassed and bullied for years.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:19:25 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Neil Sedaka, singer of Breaking Up Is Hard To Do, dies at 86</title>
    <summary>A skilled pianist nominated for five Grammy awards, Sedaka wrote hits through the 1950's and 60's.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:09:44 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Boy assaulted by birth parents wins campaign for UK child cruelty register</title>
    <summary>Tony Hudgell, who lost both legs after his birth parents assaulted him, has fought to protect children.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:28:13 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cruz Beckham launches music career, having fun amid family drama</title>
    <summary>Can David and Victoria's youngest son escape the "nepo baby" label and find success with his band?</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:14 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Soham killer Huntley still in hospital after attack using makeshift weapon</title>
    <summary>Huntley, who is serving a life sentence for murdering two schoolgirls, has significant head trauma, the BBC understands.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:07:45 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I Swear director says Baftas 'let down' Tourette's campaigner</title>
    <summary>Kirk Jones says he initially thought a slur shouted during the ceremony was not broadcast.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:14:30 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
</content-feed>
