<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content-feed source="bbc-news" generated="2026-02-27T20:35:17.958583" count="40">
  <item>
    <title>Starmer vows to fight on after historic Green by-election win</title>
    <summary>The result - in a seat Labour has held for nearly 100 years - heaps further pressure on the PM's position.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:10:29 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Henry Zeffman: Green victory shows insurgent parties are here to stay</title>
    <summary>The party's historic win in Gorton and Denton by-election is clearest sign yet of changing political landscape.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:38:15 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Soham killer Huntley still in hospital after attack using makeshift weapon</title>
    <summary>Huntley, who is serving a life sentence for murdering two schoolgirls, has significant head trauma, the BBC understands.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:07:45 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Private schools lose legal challenge over VAT changes</title>
    <summary>A group of low-fee paying private schools have challenged the government's removal of the VAT exemption.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:06:39 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'We were bullied for years before our son was killed'</title>
    <summary>The parents of 14-year-old Ibrahima Seck say they were being harassed and bullied for years.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:19:25 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cruz Beckham launches music career, having fun amid family drama</title>
    <summary>Can David and Victoria's youngest son escape the "nepo baby" label and find success with his band?</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:14 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Anxious days inside Iran as speculation grows of US strikes</title>
    <summary>To many, Iran now seems to be hovering in a tense limbo where everything could change suddenly.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:48:48 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Palestine Action arrest as Churchill statue defaced</title>
    <summary>The Westminster statue of the former prime minister is vandalised with slogans daubed in red paint.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:30:55 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tram derails in Milan, leaving one dead and dozens injured</title>
    <summary>The crowded tram was travelling in the centre of Milan at rush hour when it appeared to crash into the side of a building.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:30:00 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Letter featuring drawings by young Queen Elizabeth II sells for £25k</title>
    <summary>The letter was written when Princess Elizabeth would have been between 10 and 12 years old.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:35:52 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
</content-feed>
