<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content-feed source="bbc-middle-east" generated="2026-02-28T12:10:58.707729" count="38">
  <item>
    <title>Watch: Smoke rises in Tehran as explosions heard across country</title>
    <summary>The BBC's Jon Donnison in Jerusalem reports as Trump says "major combat operations" have begun.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:54:35 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>What we know about the joint US-Israel attack on Iran</title>
    <summary>Donald Trump has described "major combat operations", with explosions heard across Iran.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:06:22 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Aid groups in Gaza and West Bank thrown lifeline as Israel court pauses ban threat</title>
    <summary>Dozens of well-known groups faced shutdown under a new Israeli law, although the reprieve might be temporary.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:31:27 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'They seized everything': Yemen's Houthi rebels drive aid groups to the brink</title>
    <summary>Aid groups - a lifeline for millions of Yemenis - are being squeezed out of existence in areas under the control of the rebels, the BBC hears.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:15:27 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Epstein tried to buy a palace in Morocco days before his arrest in 2019</title>
    <summary>The disgraced financier was in talks to buy luxury abode Bin Ennakhi - but the purchase was never completed.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:02:12 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Israeli soldiers shot a Palestinian boy and stood around as he bled to death, video shows</title>
    <summary>Israeli forces blocked Palestinian ambulances while a 14-year-old lay bleeding for at least 45 minutes.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:01:11 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'People are getting poorer': How Iran's struggling economy is changing how families live</title>
    <summary>The soaring cost of living has left people struggling to afford basic items - creating pressures which led to mass protests.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:44:21 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>US embassy to provide passport services at West Bank settlements</title>
    <summary>Israel's government welcomes the US decision, but the Palestinian Authority says it is a clear violation of international law.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:04:21 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Trump hits out at reports that top US general warned against attacking Iran</title>
    <summary>General Dan Caine has warned that strikes against Iran could be risky, potentially drawing the US into a prolonged conflict, US media report.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:01:54 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lawyers appeal to UN over men jailed in alleged power struggle in UAE</title>
    <summary>The son of one tells the BBC how 11 years spent in prison has taken a toll on his father's health.</summary>
    <media type="none"/>
    <published>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:56:09 GMT</published>
    <category>news</category>
  </item>
</content-feed>
