<content-feed>
  <source>cnn-top-stories</source>
  <source-type>rss</source-type>
  <feed-url>http://rss.cnn.com/rss/edition.rss</feed-url>
  <generated>2026-02-28T01:46:06.317612</generated>
  <count>10</count>
  <item id="1" rank="95">
    <title>Haberman reveals why Trump attacked judge and his family in speech</title>
    <summary>CNN political contributor Maggie Haberman explains the reasoning behind Donald Trump's attacks on the judge and his family during a speech at his Mar-a-Lago resort after he was arraigned on felony charges.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2023/04/05/maggie-haberman-donald-trump-speech-indictment-reaction-sot-cnntm-vpx.cnn</link>
    <published>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 13:30:09 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="2" rank="85">
    <title>Video shows moment of deadly explosion at cafe in Russia</title>
    <summary>A well-known Russian military blogger, Vladlen Tatarsky, was killed in an explosion at a cafe in St. Petersburg, authorities said. CNN's Matthew Chance reports.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2023/04/02/russian-military-blogger-vladlen-tatarsky-killed-cafe-explosion-chance-vpx.cnn</link>
    <published>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 01:08:44 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="3" rank="75">
    <title>Why did Finland's PM lose? Reporter explains the key issue voters cared about</title>
    <summary>Finland's left-wing Prime Minister Sanna Marin conceded defeat in the country's parliamentary election as the opposition right-wing National Coalition Party claimed victory in a tightly fought contest. CNN's Laila Harrak spoke with New York Times' Chief Diplomatic Corresponden...</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2023/04/03/finland-prime-minister-sanna-marin-concedes-election-right-wing-party-wins-ovn-intl-ldn-vpx.cnn</link>
    <published>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 10:06:11 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="4" rank="75">
    <title>Finland's Prime Minister Sanna Marin concedes election</title>
    <summary>Finland's left-wing Prime Minister Sanna Marin conceded defeat on Sunday in the Nordic country's parliamentary election as the opposition right-wing National Coalition Party (NCP) claimed victory in a tightly fought contest.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/02/europe/sanna-marin-finland-elections-concedes-intl/index.html</link>
    <published>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 10:24:55 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="5" rank="70">
    <title>Suspected Chinese spy balloon was able to transmit information back to Beijing</title>
    <summary>The suspected Chinese spy balloon that transited the US earlier this year was able to capture imagery and collect some signals intelligence from US military sites, a source familiar with the matter tells CNN.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/03/politics/chinese-spy-balloon/index.html</link>
    <published>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 13:38:22 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="6" rank="70">
    <title>'Scary, cold, hungry and lonely': Volunteer soldier shares experience on front line</title>
    <summary>A young volunteer soldier, Akula, who signed up for the war at the beginning of the Russian invasion is now dealing with the trauma of war. He spoke to CNN's David McKenzie about his time on the front lines and how it has affected his mental health.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2023/04/03/soldiers-russia-ukraine-war-david-mckenzie-pkg-ovn-intl-ldn-vpx.cnn</link>
    <published>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:13:24 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="7" rank="65">
    <title>Russian authorities detain suspect over St. Petersburg cafe blast</title>
    <summary />
    <link>https://edition.cnn.com/webview/europe/live-news/russia-ukraine-war-news-04-03-23/index.html</link>
    <published>2026-02-28T01:46:06.317119</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="8" rank="65">
    <title>Wall Street Journal reporter Evan Gershkovich appeals against arrest, Russian state media says</title>
    <summary />
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/collections/intl-ukraine-030423/</link>
    <published>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 13:58:58 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="9" rank="65">
    <title>Beijing promised to 'fight back' over Taiwan leader's US visit. But this time it has more to lose</title>
    <summary>An anticipated meeting between Taiwan's President Tsai Ing-wen and US House Speaker Kevin McCarthy in California this week has sparked concerns of a repeat of the pressure campaign China launched last year when then-Speaker Nancy Pelosi visited Taipei.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/04/asia/tsai-ing-wen-taiwan-mccarthy-meeting-analysis-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
    <published>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:49:53 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="10" rank="65">
    <title>The four astronauts NASA picked for the first crewed moon mission in 50 years</title>
    <summary>Astronauts who will helm the first crewed moon mission in five decades were revealed on Monday, queuing up the quartet to begin training for the historic Artemis II lunar flyby that is set to take off in November 2024.</summary>
    <link>https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/03/world/artemis-2-astronaut-crew-scn/index.html</link>
    <published>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 11:44:30 GMT</published>
    <original-source>cnn-top-stories</original-source>
  </item>
</content-feed>