<content-feed>
  <source>jerusalem-post-israel</source>
  <source-type>rss</source-type>
  <feed-url>https://www.jpost.com/rss/rssfeedsisraelnews.aspx</feed-url>
  <generated>2026-02-28T01:46:03.984039</generated>
  <count>10</count>
  <item id="1" rank="115">
    <title>Supreme Court allows NGOs facing Gaza ban to keep operating, for now</title>
    <summary>Some 17 NGOs and the Association of International Development Agencies (AIDA) sought an urgent suspension of the ban in a petition to the High Court of Justice.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-888220</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:35:31 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="2" rank="115">
    <title>Huckabee tells US Embassy staff in Israel to leave today amid Iran strike fears</title>
    <summary>Multiple countries have urged nationals in Israel to exercise extreme caution, including China, France, and Italy, while others urged citizens to leave Iran, including the UK, Canada, and Australia</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/defense-news/article-888204</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:42:37 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="3" rank="110">
    <title>IDF Brig. Gen. says still no change to public guidelines amid Iran tensions</title>
    <summary>"The IDF is closely monitoring the situation in Iran and is alert and prepared to defend you," he said in the video statement.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-888224</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 19:01:30 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="4" rank="110">
    <title>IDF says ceasefire violated in Rafah incident, conducts overnight strikes</title>
    <summary>The IDF also said it carried out additional precise strikes overnight into Friday against several armed Hamas terrorists in the Rafah area.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/defense-news/article-888207</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:33:27 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="5" rank="95">
    <title>Israeli elections: New poll shows Eisenkot gain, Bennett dip, blocs frozen at 60–50</title>
    <summary>Despite shifts among individual party leaders, the overall balance between the blocs remains unchanged: 60 seats for the opposition and 50 for the coalition.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/article-888200</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:42:30 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="6" rank="90">
    <title>Far-right activists harass Arab-Israeli journalist outside her home</title>
    <summary>At least 20 protesters stood at the entrance of the journalist’s apartment building, shouting slogans such as "Let the IDF win, fuck the Arabs,” and "Inshallah you have a heart attack."</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-888225</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 19:35:08 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="7" rank="85">
    <title>Salvador Litvak brings his film 'Guns &amp; Moses' to Israel</title>
    <summary>Speaking about how he had decided to make the film, he said, “My wife, Nina, and I set out to make a Jewish mystery thriller in a world that Hollywood never depicts on film - our world."</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/culture/article-888217</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:48:53 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="8" rank="70">
    <title>From Israeli sitcoms to HBO hits: The best streaming picks for Purim</title>
    <summary>TV Time: Purim is coming up, what should you watch to get in the spirit?</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/culture/article-888165</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 23:15:09 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="9" rank="70">
    <title>Left-wing activists hospitalized following settler attack in West Bank village</title>
    <summary>The victims were taken to Beilinson Hospital in Petah Tikva to be treated for head injuries.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-888221</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:00:14 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
  <item id="10" rank="70">
    <title>Israel 2048: New report by Henry Jackson Society looks at possible future strategy for Israel</title>
    <summary>This is an important new contribution to the discussion about what comes next for Israel and the Middle East, rooting Israel’s strategy in Israel’s history and in the West.</summary>
    <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/defense-news/article-888212</link>
    <published>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:51:05 GMT</published>
    <original-source>jerusalem-post-israel</original-source>
  </item>
</content-feed>