<content-feed>
  <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  <source-type>reddit</source-type>
  <generated>2026-02-28T02:04:35.112409</generated>
  <count>10</count>
  <subreddit>IsraelPalestine</subreddit>
  <item id="1" rank="125.9" reddit_score="59">
    <title>Why has Egypt refused to let any Gazans evacuate during the Israel-Hamas war? Isn't blocking civilians from fleeing against international law?</title>
    <summary>During the war between Hamas and Israel, Egypt has kept the Rafah border crossing mostly closed and has not allowed almost any Gazans to evacuate to safety. Their president Sisi even said publicly "not a single Gazan will be allowed in."

This is confusing because Egyptians and G</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfegx6/why_has_egypt_refused_to_let_any_gazans_evacuate/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfegx6/why_has_egypt_refused_to_let_any_gazans_evacuate/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T18:17:37</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="2" rank="106.0" reddit_score="10">
    <title>How do I learn about the Israel Palestine war?</title>
    <summary>I want to learn about it to form a good opinion. I'm currently in support of Palestine (I don't like violence in either side though), I don't think that will change, but I want to know more about the war. Recently I was researching about hamas and learned things I didn't previous</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfuzx3/how_do_i_learn_about_the_israel_palestine_war/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfuzx3/how_do_i_learn_about_the_israel_palestine_war/</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T04:59:19</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="3" rank="105" reddit_score="128">
    <title>The fake narrative of Israel targeting journalists is unraveling</title>
    <summary>Early on in the Gaza war, headlines across the world were dominated by the emotionaly powerful claim that Israel was deliberately targeting journalists. This was an effort to frame the conflict not just as a military war but as an assault on the freedom of the press itself. The i</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1regj1x/the_fake_narrative_of_israel_targeting/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1regj1x/the_fake_narrative_of_israel_targeting/</url>
    <published>2026-02-25T17:37:43</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="4" rank="83.8" reddit_score="38">
    <title>TL;DR: Why are we so one sided now?</title>
    <summary>Why is having ANY kind of discussion about this war go south so quickly? The second you try and have a conversation about this that doesn’t immediately lead you to be pro-Palestine, you get looked at like scum. I feel like there are layers to this but noone wants to discuss that.</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfjakh/tldr_why_are_we_so_one_sided_now/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfjakh/tldr_why_are_we_so_one_sided_now/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T21:10:11</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="5" rank="83.8" reddit_score="38">
    <title>Al-Jazeera News Articles Always Miss the First Half of the Story?</title>
    <summary>Let's look at this news article which describes a riot by Israeli settlers in the West Bank on Feb 13 and lasted until 15: https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2026/2/13/israeli-settlers-injure-dozens-of-palestinians-in-wave-of-west-bank-attacks

It does read like those Israeli settler</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rdngof/aljazeera_news_articles_always_miss_the_first/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rdngof/aljazeera_news_articles_always_miss_the_first/</url>
    <published>2026-02-24T19:59:21</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="6" rank="82.3" reddit_score="23">
    <title>My take if whack lmk</title>
    <summary>I’ve been following the October 7th war since it started, and over time I’ve noticed my perspective diverging from a lot of the dominant online narratives.

Part of that shift came from early commentary that felt dismissive in ways I didn’t understand. For example, when the Israe</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfzfm9/my_take_if_whack_lmk/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfzfm9/my_take_if_whack_lmk/</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T08:44:53</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="7" rank="81.8" reddit_score="18">
    <title>Israel has for the first time in 20 years lost popular support in the US.</title>
    <summary>Before I begin, losing support means politics is next on line. In 2024, there were minor attempts to pillory pro-Israel candidates which failed and I think the trend would largely continue and intensify well into 2026 primaries and 2028 general.

Firstly, the result is from Gallu</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rg53i4/israel_has_for_the_first_time_in_20_years_lost/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rg53i4/israel_has_for_the_first_time_in_20_years_lost/</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T14:15:04</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="8" rank="79.1" reddit_score="41">
    <title>Why do so many podcasts/alternative media only talk about Israel.</title>
    <summary>It is very noticeable that certain alternative media outlets which used to cover a large range of topics at this point devote around 90% of their platform to stories that are in some way related to Israel. Scroll through their media page on Youtube lately and its basically.

Isra</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rcrv1p/why_do_so_many_podcastsalternative_media_only/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rcrv1p/why_do_so_many_podcastsalternative_media_only/</url>
    <published>2026-02-23T21:51:11</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="9" rank="76.6" reddit_score="16">
    <title>Quick question for one state solution supporters about the universality of their solution</title>
    <summary>Quick question for the supporters of a 1 state solution: Which of the these other historical or modern conflicts or disputes do you believe should be resolved or should have been resolved with a one state solution?

Russia Ukraine

Japan China

Russia Georgia 

Russia Chechnya 

</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfb61w/quick_question_for_one_state_solution_supporters/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rfb61w/quick_question_for_one_state_solution_supporters/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T16:10:57</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
  <item id="10" rank="75.8" reddit_score="8">
    <title>A question of legitimacy over creating cultures for political purposes.</title>
    <summary>How does this help peace in the middle east if we're just going to pretend propaganda tools like this aren't the norm rather than the exception ? It seems obvious the entire charade was invented after the failed aggression of the Arab states against Israel in 67.   
  
So why hav</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rcx4on/a_question_of_legitimacy_over_creating_cultures/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/IsraelPalestine/comments/1rcx4on/a_question_of_legitimacy_over_creating_cultures/</url>
    <published>2026-02-24T01:05:55</published>
    <source>reddit_r_IsraelPalestine</source>
  </item>
</content-feed>