<content-feed>
  <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  <source-type>reddit</source-type>
  <generated>2026-02-28T02:04:12.243149</generated>
  <count>10</count>
  <subreddit>Jewish</subreddit>
  <item id="1" rank="110" reddit_score="459">
    <title>A Letter to Progressive Friends</title>
    <summary>Dear Progressives,

I've been trying to find the right words, but I can't. So here goes: If you're ceaselessly posting only about Gaza / Israel, and not Iran, Sudan, Ukraine, or Burma - you're guilty of the selective empathy you're accusing others of. You said nothing during the </summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rexwy7/a_letter_to_progressive_friends/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rexwy7/a_letter_to_progressive_friends/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T04:26:53</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="2" rank="100.0" reddit_score="50">
    <title>Can Iranian Jews legally emigrate? Also, are any of the Jews arrested following the Twelve-Day war still in Iranian custody?</title>
    <summary>Getting conflicting information for both these questions on Google. I saw an interesting article by The Atlantic on the topic but it is paywalled.

I read somewhere that on paper Jews can legally emigrate, but in practice the government restricts passports and places families und</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfet49/can_iranian_jews_legally_emigrate_also_are_any_of/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfet49/can_iranian_jews_legally_emigrate_also_are_any_of/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T18:29:40</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="3" rank="85" reddit_score="438">
    <title>ADL ‘appalled’ CAIR leader invokes blood libel that Israel skins Palestinian bodies for organ harvesting before Ohio state Senate</title>
    <summary>**The antisemitic group's Ohio executive director accused Israel of operating the "largest human skin bank in the world."**

"The Anti-Defamation League said that it was “appalled” after Khalid Turaani, Ohio region executive director of the Council on American–Islamic Relations, </summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rf3q9o/adl_appalled_cair_leader_invokes_blood_libel_that/</link>
    <url>https://www.jns.org/adl-appalled-cair-leader-invokes-blood-libel-before-ohio-state-senate/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T09:23:32</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="4" rank="85" reddit_score="235">
    <title>About the anti-Israel boycott of 'Scream 7' and Melissa Barrera's Antisemitism</title>
    <summary>I am making this deep-dive post since ***Scream 7*** is releasing in theaters this weekend.

You may have seen pro-Palestine Leftists online pushing a boycott of the new movie Scream 7. I am making this post to clarify and explain the situation. This boycott was officially endors</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1reo1cz/about_the_antiisrael_boycott_of_scream_7_and/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/gallery/1reo1cz</url>
    <published>2026-02-25T21:59:00</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="5" rank="80" reddit_score="147">
    <title>Antisemites Spying on Us</title>
    <summary>\[\[ TRIGGER WARNING \]\] if seeing violent antisemitism and Jewish hate triggers you please swipe off this post

I was scrolling on X looking at pictures of punch the monkey, sure you guys know the cute little guy. Found a post and clicked on the comments and the first reply was</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfzurf/antisemites_spying_on_us/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfzurf/antisemites_spying_on_us/</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T09:09:36</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="6" rank="78.9" reddit_score="39">
    <title>Children's surnames - husband isn't Jewish</title>
    <summary>Hi all,

  
My fiance and I both want children. He is happy to raise them Jewish. However, he wants them to take his last name which is not even remotely Jewish sounding. I'll be keeping my last name - we've already agreed on that. He will not take my last name and I completely u</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1reocsx/childrens_surnames_husband_isnt_jewish/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1reocsx/childrens_surnames_husband_isnt_jewish/</url>
    <published>2026-02-25T22:10:16</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="7" rank="70" reddit_score="367">
    <title>Identity crisis after taking an ancestry test as an Italian and not being even 1% Italian</title>
    <summary>I knew I was jewish, but I did not grow up as it being a part of my identity and did not grow up religious at all, in a sense I grew up more christian than jewish. I come from Italy and I guess I never felt like I was a different ethnicity, or look any different than other Italia</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rgamke/identity_crisis_after_taking_an_ancestry_test_as/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/gallery/1rgamke</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T18:02:02</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="8" rank="70" reddit_score="179">
    <title>My Jewish friend passed away and I need help respecting her correctly.</title>
    <summary>Edit: Thank you all for your very kind and useful advice. This is all extremely stressful and heart wrenching. I have a lot to work with from the comment section and I've made a list of things that I need to get done. I'll keep reading comments as they come in and I'll try to rem</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfh1ha/my_jewish_friend_passed_away_and_i_need_help/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rfh1ha/my_jewish_friend_passed_away_and_i_need_help/</url>
    <published>2026-02-26T19:48:51</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="9" rank="69.9" reddit_score="49">
    <title>Targeted in a video game for being Jewish.</title>
    <summary>I feel kinda silly sharing this. 

It’s hard to explain. This shook me, really disturbed me, and I want to throw it out there to see if you all think I’m being too sensitive.


There’s this video game called arc raiders. And I know, shocking, antisemitism and video games… but how</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rgmd6e/targeted_in_a_video_game_for_being_jewish/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rgmd6e/targeted_in_a_video_game_for_being_jewish/</url>
    <published>2026-02-28T01:21:52</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
  <item id="10" rank="67.3" reddit_score="23">
    <title>Going to my first Purim celebration at local synagogue...</title>
    <summary>I called the local Reform synagogue today and told them I would like to attend their Purim celebration next week. They said there would be a play, coffee, and hamantaschen (which I have never tried, but the lady I talked to said they were "yummy"). 

  
I am a non-Jew, and this w</summary>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rgj3ys/going_to_my_first_purim_celebration_at_local/</link>
    <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/Jewish/comments/1rgj3ys/going_to_my_first_purim_celebration_at_local/</url>
    <published>2026-02-27T23:13:49</published>
    <source>reddit_r_Jewish</source>
  </item>
</content-feed>